How's that?
HOW'S THAT? [screaming]
HOW'S THAT? HOW'S THAT? HOW'S THAT?
[screaming]
How's that?
>> [cheering and laughter]
>> That's how y'all set THAT
GUYS. So proud of you, man. So proud of
you. Talk about complimentary football
at its finest. Complimentary football.
All three phases dominate. ALL THREE
PHASES straight dominate. Run for over
200 yards on the [cheering]
[applause]
192 YDS RUSHING TO 42.
150 YARDS RUSHING OFFENSIVELY.
[cheering and applause]
>> NO SACKS ALLOWED.
>> No sacks allowed.
Hey,
Parker Washington.
[cheering]
PARKER WASHINGTON, GET OUT.
>> How about our quarterback of Parker
Washington at the
[applause]
six total touchdowns?
[cheering]
How about our quarterback, man?
>> How about our freaking quarterback
[cheering]
>> again? How about our quarterback
defensively? Y'all were on today, boys.
Un.
TALK ABOUT THREE TAKEAWAYS, GUYS, IN
FOUR STRAIGHT [cheering] GAMES. THAT'S
THE FIRST TIME EVER. THREE INTERCEPTIONS
on defense.
[applause]
HOW ABOUT OUR DEFENSE WITH A UNION?
[cheering]
How about Devin?
>> Devon Hamilton and the game.
Unbelievable job.
[cheering]
HEY JOSH HINES ALLEN TYING THE FRANCHISE
RECORD.
>> [cheering]
>> AND WE HAD AN UNBELIEVABLE moment
obviously happen for our franchise